B2.
Listen to Amy and her friend James talking about the things they make at home.
Complete the notes below. Hi, Amy.
I hope you liked the tie-dying workshop yesterday.
Oh yes, it was great.
I like learning new skills and making things myself.
Do you do things like that at home?
Yes, one of my favourite activities is cooking.
That's a great skill to have. I know.
I love to cook traditional Chinese food.
What about you?
I love making things.
We have a small vegetable garden and I often help my mum look after it.
I made a bird box and a little house for bees. That's cool.
I love making cute clothes for my pet cat.
That sounds like fun.
I also like fixing things around the home.
For example, I sometimes fix my parents' bikes. How nice!